so you were white and Christian so like
you're aligning with the base of this
country but I I feel like there's
there's an understanding that says like
if someone doesn't agree with you it may
come from the fact that they have had a
completely different experience I
totally agree you have had a I have had
nothing of similarity to your experience
in this country literally nothing and so
when like for me it's an insult to me
that you don't want to speak because
you're not you're not you're not
listening to what I'm saying you spoke
because you were urged to and given a
floor to he spoke she spoke she spoke
but she didn't want to she was urged
that's what I'm saying so what I'm
saying is
that all of us here have had such unique
experiences and just from such different
backgrounds that we have to like if this
is a a conversation about having
conversations then we have to be
listening to each other and listening to
the fact that like the reason am so
passionate and I'm not hostile I'm
passionate the reason I am so passionate
is because I've had such a different
experience in this country than you
because as a black woman the government
is so much in my life and it always has
been like there the government literally
said that black men couldn't even be in
the house or else women could not get
welfare and that's a big reason why
there's such a Chasm between black women
and black men in this generation so I
think that there's just a lot to
understand for like why people are
talking the way they're talking about
different things I understand why you're
talking the way you're talking cuz I
know because I just don't understand
what am I talking I just said I believe
in this country yes and you can say that
in a way that I cannot because you've
had a different experience because this
country is here for you this country
ain't here for me in the same way sis it
isn't and you as a trans person have to
also identify the fact that this country
hasn't been here for Trans until like
maybe 2 o00 today so that's a constant
that's a constant I do think I totally
agree the sense that I certainly grew up
different than a lot of people uh but I
you think that I I didn't have any I had
so many no I'm not saying you didn't
have any issu many issues in my issues
but your issues may not have come from
the the positioning that you have in
Amica